- Class, it's everyone's favorite time of year.
同学们，这是一年中最受欢迎的时刻。
- Heirloom tomato season? - No.
是传家宝番茄季节吗？
- Taco season?
不。
- That's not a thing.
是玉米卷季节吗？
- I think what Mr. Williams is referring to
那不是个事。
is the upcoming election for class president.
我想威廉姆斯先生指的是即将举行的班长选举。
- So when you mean
所以当你说
"everyone's favorite time of year,"
“一年中最受欢迎的时刻”，
you mean just Ricky's?
你指的是只有里基的吗？
- That's correct, Dawn.
没错，道恩。
But this year we're going to jazz it up a bit
但今年我们要稍微提升一下氛围
with online polling
通过在线投票
that will tell us minute to minute
这将实时告诉我们
who the most popular candidate is.
谁是最受欢迎的候选人。
- Ooh, I hope there will be graphs.
哦，我希望会有图表。
Perhaps a bar graph, a histogram,
也许是一个条形图，一个直方图，
or, dare I say it, a scatterplot.
或者，我敢说，一个散点图。
- You know very well
你很清楚
there will be a scatterplot, Ricky.
会有一个散点图，Ricky。
You helped design the app.
你参与了应用的设计。
- I'd also like to help design the future of this school,
我也希望能参与设计这所学校的未来，
which is why I'd like to announce my candidacy
这也是为什么我想宣布我参选
for class president.
班级主席。
It would be an honor to serve you all.
能为你们服务将是一种荣幸。
- I wish you'd serve me some pizza right now,
我希望你现在能给我来点披萨，
because I'd like to announce
因为我想要宣布
that I am hungry.
我现在饿了。
- Does anyone else want to run for president?
还有其他人想竞选主席吗？
So far in all my classes, no one is running but Ricky.
到目前为止，在我所有的班级里，除了Ricky没有人参选。
- Dawn, you should run.
Dawn，你应该参选。
You're popular,
你很受欢迎，
you're a leader on the soccer field,
你在足球场上是个领袖，
and most importantly,
最重要的是，
I'd be best friends with the president.
我会成为总统最好的朋友。
- Aw, thanks, Mae, but I don't know.
- 哦，谢谢，梅，但我不知道。
I think Ricky would be a good president,
我觉得里基会是个好总统，
and it's really not my thing.
而且这真的不是我的菜。
- Thank you, Dawn.
- 谢谢你，唐。
I would make a good president.
我会成为一个好总统。
And she's right, Mae.
而且她是对的，梅。
It's really not her thing.
这真的不是她擅长的。
- Well, what do you mean, it's not my thing?
- 那么，你是什么意思，这不是我的事？
- Hey, you're the one who said, "It's not my thing."
- 嘿，是你自己说的，“这不是我的事。”
And I agree.
我同意。
It's not your thing.
这不是你的事。
- Well, you don't get to say it's not my thing.
- 好吧，你不能说这不是我的事。
Only I get to say what my thing is.
只有我能决定什么是我的事。
- Look, it's not a bad thing you know it's not your thing.
- 看，你知道这不是你的事并不是坏事。
That's a good thing.
这是件好事。
- Well, here's the thing.
- 好吧，事情是这样的。
Mind your own thing.
管好你自己的事。
- Uh-oh.
哎呀。
- Looks like we might have a thing.
看来我们可能有点问题。
- I want to run for president.
我想竞选总统。
- Hey, that's my thing.
嘿，那是我的事。
- We'll see about that.
我们走着瞧。
- Ooh, the scatterplot thickens.
哦，散点图变得复杂了。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na na na na na na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- ♪ Hey ♪
♪ 嘿 ♪
♪
- President Dawn.
总统Dawn。
Yeah, that's got a nice ring to it.
嗯，听起来不错。
I wonder what my campaign slogan should be.
我想知道我的竞选口号应该是什么。
- How about, "Vote for Dawn.
比如，“投Dawn一票。
"I don't really want to be president.
“我其实不想当总统。
I just want to annoy Ricky?"
“我只是想惹恼Ricky？”
Oh, and by the way, it's not working.
哦，顺便说一句，这招不灵。
- Uh, what's going on?
呃，发生什么事了？
- Ricky and Dawn are both running for class president.
Ricky和Dawn都在竞选班长。
Yeah, things are getting a little saucy.
是的，事情变得有点火辣了。
- Saucy?
- 辛辣？
Sauce.
酱料。
Pizzas have sauce.
披萨有酱料。
Refrigerators have pizza.
冰箱里有披萨。
We have a refrigerator.
我们有一个冰箱。
Pizza!
披萨！
- Hey, look, I'm proud of both of you,
- 嘿，听着，我为你们俩感到骄傲，
but campaign nicely,
但请好好竞选，
because one of you is going to win,
因为你们中有一个会赢，
and one of you is going to lose.
另一个会输。
But no matter what happens,
但无论发生什么，
I'm gonna be the mother of the winner.
我都会是赢家的妈妈。
Yay!
耶！
Oh, and the loser.
哦，还有输家的。
Aw.
哎。
- [clears throat]
（清嗓子）
Hello there, family.
大家好，家人们。
Have you ever wanted to take a selfie
你们有没有想过自拍，
and realized your arm was too short?
却发现手臂不够长？
all: No!
大家：没有！
- Me too!
我也是！
And the only option was looking like an idiot
唯一的办法就是看起来像个傻瓜
with one of these ridiculous selfie poles.
拿着这些可笑的自拍杆。
Well, say good-bye to your problems
好吧，跟你的问题说再见
and say hello to Tom's Get Stealthy Pole.
向汤姆的隐形杆问好。
- Oh!
哦！
Tom!
汤姆！
- Behold, the perfect stealthy selfie.
看，完美的隐形自拍。
- You look horrible.
你看起来很糟糕。
- You're right.
你说得对。
Oh, it's the lighting.
哦，是光线问题。
You know where the lighting's perfect?
你知道哪里光线最好吗？
In the living room over by the good china.
客厅那边摆着好瓷器的地方。
- Tom, no.
汤姆，不行。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不行，不行，不行，不行，不行，不行，不行，不行。
- Well, I'm off to prepare for tomorrow's debate.
好吧，我要去准备明天的辩论了。
I'll be upstairs practicing
我会在楼上练习，
against the only worthy opponent I have:
对抗我唯一值得的对手：
myself in the mirror.
镜子里的自己。
- How are you gonna prepare, Dawn?
你打算怎么准备，Dawn？
- Oh, I'm just gonna wing it.
- 哦，我就随便应付一下。
- Wing it?
- 随便应付？
Wings.
翅膀。
Chicken wings.
鸡翅。
Phones order wings.
手机点鸡翅。
I have a phone.
我有手机。
- Wing it?
- 随便应付？
What does that even mean?
那是什么意思？
- It means I'm gonna do what I do on the soccer field:
- 意思是我会在足球场上怎么做：
keep my eye on the ball, see how things develop,
盯着球，观察局势发展，
and let the game come to me.
让比赛来找我。
- [gasps] That's adorable.
- [喘气] 真可爱。
Okay, Dawn, you wing it.
好吧，Dawn，你自由发挥。
- Is this Wing My Bell?
- 这是“摇铃点餐”吗？
Yeah, I'd like to order
是的，我想点
one "Wing, Wing, Wing, Hello?" Bucket.
一份“翅膀，翅膀，翅膀，你好？”桶。
- This debate is gonna be like shooting fish in a barrel.
- 这场辩论将会像在桶里射鱼一样简单。
- Oh, do you have fish in a barrel?
- 哦，你桶里有鱼吗？
- They're not gonna have--
- 他们不会有——
- Oh, you do?
- 哦，你有？
Fried or grilled?
炸的还是烤的？
♪ ♪
- Oh, the length's fine.
- 哦，长度正好。
Let's just take a little off the top, Steve.
我们就稍微剪一点，Steve。
[gasps]
[倒吸一口气]
My hair's back.
我的头发回来了。
It's a dream come true.
梦想成真了。
Come to Papa.
来爸爸这里。
Oh, Tom.
哦，Tom。
Do you play the drums?
你会打鼓吗？
Because this picture is banging!
因为这张照片太炸了！
This baby is going straight to FaceShack.com.
这张宝贝直接上FaceShack.com。
- Photo uploaded.
照片已上传。
- [snoring]
[打呼噜]
- Vote for Ricky.
投票给Ricky。
- Uh, hey, Dad, have you seen Ricky?
呃，嘿，爸，你见过Ricky吗？
Oh, sorry, Grandpa, thought you were Dad.
哦，对不起，爷爷，我以为你是爸爸。
- Hilarious.
太搞笑了。
But if you'd done your research instead of winging it,
但如果你做了研究而不是临时抱佛脚，
you'd know that a sweater/jacket combo
你就会知道毛衣/夹克组合
conveys a sense of authority, confidence, and approachability.
传达出一种权威、自信和亲和力。
- Well, I'm confident this is about to approach you.
- 嗯，我确信这很快就会接近你。
- Ow! Ew, ew, ew!
- 哎哟！呸，呸，呸！
- And that's called winging it.
- 这就是所谓的即兴发挥。
What's all that?
这都是些什么？
- My research also showed the school store
- 我的研究还显示学校商店
is a great campaigning location.
是一个绝佳的竞选地点。
- Well, yeah, I'm gonna put my posters up there too.
- 嗯，是的，我也打算在那里贴我的海报。
Just got to make some.
只是得先做出来。
- Ooh, sorry, Dawn.
- 哦，对不起，Dawn。
I've got an exclusive deal with Nicky.
我有一个和Nicky的独家协议。
- When Ricky becomes president,
当Ricky成为总统时，
he's promised to get me a cushy mat to stand on.
他答应给我一个舒适的垫子站。
That'll feel real good on a working man's feet.
这对一个工人的脚来说会感觉很好。
[chiming] - Oh, weird.
哦，奇怪。
The polling app shows I'm winning.
投票应用显示我领先。
Told you this is my thing.
告诉过你这是我的强项。
Have a button.
给你一个按钮。
- Yeah, well, your buttons aren't as cool as mine.
是啊，不过你的按钮没我的酷。
Just got to make some.
我得做一些。
- Settle down, everyone.
大家冷静一下。
I know it's a little warm in here,
我知道这里有点热，
so let's get this debate under way.
所以让我们开始这场辩论吧。
The first question will be...
第一个问题将是...
Mae.
Mae。
- My question is for Dawn.
我的问题是给Dawn的。
I think you're awesome, and I'm gonna vote for you.
我觉得你很棒，我会投票给你。
- Do you have a question, Mae?
Mae，你有什么问题吗？
- I'm gonna vote for you?
我会投票给你吗？
- Next up?
接下来呢？
Jennifer.
- Uh, it's pronounced "Dicky."
呃，它应该念作“Dicky”。
My question is about the bathroom.
我的问题是关于浴室的。
- I'm way ahead of you.
我早就想到了。
I've already done a cost-benefit analysis
我已经做了更换更柔软卫生纸的成本效益分析，
of getting softer toilet paper, so vote for me,
所以投我一票，
and you'll be getting this instead of this.
你将会得到这个而不是这个。
[applause]
（掌声）
- Actually, I meant the bathroom at home.
实际上，我指的是家里的浴室。
Is your toothbrush the green one or the yellow one?
你的牙刷是绿色的还是黄色的？
Because I've been using both.
因为我两个都用过。
- Okay, thank you, Jennifer.
- 好的，谢谢你，詹妮弗。
Dawn, would you like to address
道恩，你想谈谈卫生纸的问题吗？
the toilet tissue issue?
- 呃，这是我第一次听说卫生纸的问题。
- Um, this is the first issue I've heard
- 意料之中。
with the toilet tissue.
- 但作为你们的总统，
- Surprise, surprise.
我保证会彻底解决这个问题。
- But as your president,
[笑] 明白吗？底部？
I promise to get to the bottom of it.
好的。
[laughing] Get it? Bottom?
- 很高兴你觉得这都是个笑话，道恩，
Okay.
好的。
- Glad you think this is all a joke, Dawn,
— 很高兴你觉得这都是笑话，Dawn，
but these good people are voting for a class president,
但这些善良的人们是在选举班级主席，
not a class clown.
不是在选班级小丑。
[applause]
（掌声）
- Wow, he's authoritative, approachable, and confident.
— 哇，他既有权威，又平易近人，还自信满满。
He has got this working man's vote.
他赢得了我们这些普通工人的选票。
- Next question.
— 下一个问题。
- I have a question.
— 我有个问题。
Ricky, why are you sweating so much?
Ricky，你为什么出这么多汗？
- I'm not sweating.
- 我没出汗。
Next question.
下一个问题。
- Um, yes, you are sweating.
- 呃，是的，你在出汗。
Are you nervous?
你紧张吗？
- [scoffs] No.
- [嗤之以鼻] 不。
Any other questions?
还有其他问题吗？
Jennifer, didn't you have one?
詹妮弗，你不是有一个问题吗？
- Still pronounced "Dicky."
- 还是发音为“Dicky”。
- Are you hiding something?
- 你在隐瞒什么吗？
- No, I'm approachable and confident.
- 不，我平易近人且自信。
- And sweaty.
- 还有点出汗。
Perhaps you should use
也许你应该用
that soft toilet paper to wipe your brow.
那柔软的卫生纸擦擦额头。
- I don't need you telling me what to wipe with.
- 我不需要你告诉我用什么擦。
Ah!
啊！
- Oh, the sweat stings, doesn't it?
- 哦，汗水刺痛了，是吧？
How about you tell the people what you're hiding?
不如你告诉人们你在隐瞒什么？
- I'm not hiding anything!
- 我什么也没隐瞒！
It's the sweater!
是那件毛衣！
- The sweater, huh?
- 那件毛衣，嗯？
I may not be as smooth as this guy,
我可能没有这家伙那么圆滑，
but I do know, students of Edgewood,
但我确实知道，Edgewood的学生们，
you want a president you can trust,
你们需要一个可以信赖的校长，
not a secret-keeping sweater.
而不是一个藏着秘密的毛衣。
[cheers and applause]
（欢呼和掌声）
Yeah, whoo-hoo!
耶，哇呼！
Vote for Dawn!
支持Dawn！
Thank you, thank you.
谢谢，谢谢。
Looks like this is my thing.
看来这是我的强项。
Sometimes you lose, and sometimes you wing.
有时候你会输，有时候你会赢。
Wing, wing, wing.
赢了，赢了，赢了。
- Hello?
- 喂？
- Wing, wing, wing, wing, wing, wing, wing, wing.
- 赢了，赢了，赢了，赢了，赢了，赢了，赢了，赢了。
♪ ♪
- Uh, Tom?
- 呃，汤姆？
Did you, um, I don't know, happen to post
你，嗯，我不知道，有没有在FaceShack上
a photo of us on FaceShack?
发了一张我们的照片？
- Oh, yes, I did. - Hmm. - And it's gone viral.
- 哦，是的，我发了。 - 嗯。 - 而且它火了。
[knocking]
[敲门]
It's almost at 5,000 knocks on the FaceShack door.
在FaceShack的门上几乎有5000次敲击了。
[knocking]
Ah, people love a pretty face.
啊，人们喜欢漂亮的脸蛋。
- I look horrible, Tom.
- 我看起来很糟糕，汤姆。
I am drooling.
我口水直流。
You can see up my nose.
你能看到我的鼻孔。
My tongue is hanging out of my mouth.
我的舌头伸出来了。
I look like an English bulldog.
我看起来像只英国斗牛犬。
- Hmm, yes, but I look like a majestic golden retriever.
- 嗯，是的，但我看起来像一只威严的金毛寻回犬。
- Oh.
- 哦。
- She's beating me.
- 她超过我了。
[chiming] She can't beat me.
她不可能赢我。
Stupid app.
愚蠢的应用。
Why did I create you?
我为什么要创造你？
I'm the presidential one!
我才是总统的那一个！
Me!
是我！
Look at her over there.
看她那边。
All those girls hanging on her every word.
那些女孩们全神贯注地听她说的每一句话。
- It's disgusting.
真让人恶心。
- You're right.
你说得对。
Those girls should be hanging on my every word.
那些女孩应该全神贯注地听我说的每一句话。
Ladies, how we doing today?
女士们，今天我们怎么样？
- Man, girls sure do love him.
- 伙计，女孩们确实喜欢他。
- Yes, yes, they do,
- 是的，是的，她们确实喜欢，
and soon, their love for him will turn into votes for me.
而且很快，她们对他的爱将转化为对我的投票。
- So you want to grab a smoothie?
- 所以你想去喝杯 smoothie 吗？
- Yes, yes, I do.
- 是的，是的，我想。
♪ ♪
- And to anyone who asks if I can handle the presidency,
- 对于任何问我是否能胜任总统职位的人，
I say, "No sweat."
我会说，“小菜一碟。”
[laughter]
[笑声]
- My fellow students, your attention please.
同学们，请注意。
I know you've all had a good laugh at my expense,
我知道你们都在笑我，
but here's something you won't be laughing at:
但这里有件事你们笑不出来：
my new running mate, Dicky Harper!
我的新竞选伙伴，迪基·哈珀！
[electronic music]
- Unce, unce, unce, unce, unce, unce, unce, unce, unce, unce!
咚次，咚次，咚次，咚次，咚次，咚次，咚次，咚次，咚次，咚次！
- That is so unfair.
这太不公平了。
You can't do that.
你不能这样做。
- Actually, I already cleared it with Mr. Williams,
实际上，我已经和威廉姆斯先生确认过了，
and he said, "No problem."
他说，“没问题。”
- I'm surprised you'd want to be vice president.
- 我惊讶你会想当副会长。
Is that really your thing?
那真的是你的菜吗？
- Chicks are my thing, and they like a man with power.
- 美女是我的菜，而且她们喜欢有权力的男人。
Unce with me, ladies.
跟我一起跳，女士们。
Unce, unce, unce, unce, unce, unce, unce, unce, unce!
跳，跳，跳，跳，跳，跳，跳，跳，跳！
- Uh, Dawn, have you seen the polls?
- 呃，Dawn，你看过民调了吗？
Ricky and Dicky are gaining on you.
Ricky和Dicky正在追赶你。
- What? [chiming]
- 什么？
- You know, Dawn, I finally figured out
- 你知道吗，Dawn，我终于明白了
what your thing is.
你的菜是什么。
Losing.
落后。
To me.
对我。
♪ ♪
- It's gotten even worse.
- 情况变得更糟了。
Ricky and Dicky are totally beating me now.
- Ricky和Dicky现在完全超过我了。
- Actually, they're calling themselves "Dricky."
- 实际上，他们现在自称是“Dricky”。
- Dricky?
- Dricky？
More like Ridicky.
- 更像是Ridicky。
No, I need to figure out some way to regain the advantage.
- 不，我需要想办法重新获得优势。
He has a gimmick,
- 他有一个噱头，
I need a gimmick.
我需要一个噱头。
- Oh, hey.
- 哦，嘿。
- And there he is.
- 他来了。
Excuse us, Mae.
不好意思，Mae。
Nicky, listen.
Nicky，听着。
Now that Ricky and Dicky are running mates,
既然Ricky和Dicky成了搭档，
what do you say we team up?
我们何不也组队呢？
If kids love Dricky, they'll flip for Dawnky.
如果孩子们喜欢Dricky，他们一定会为Dawnky疯狂。
Huh?
嗯？
Dawn, Nicky, Dawnky?
Dawn，Nicky，Dawnky？
Don't worry, we'll work on the name.
别担心，我们会想个好名字的。
- I don't know, Dawn.
我不知道，Dawn。
- Oh, come on.
哦，拜托。
You're the boss of the school store.
你是学校商店的老板。
You've got your finger on the pulse of the student body.
你对学生群体的脉搏了如指掌。
- Well, I do know what color notebooks
嗯，我确实知道哪种颜色的笔记本
are gonna sell out first.
会最先卖光。
- Yeah.
是啊。
You know, you're a powerful guy.
你知道，你是个有影响力的人。
Kids trust you.
孩子们信任你。
That's your thing.
那是你的专长。
- It is my thing.
确实是我的专长。
- You know, imagine your face all over these walls.
想象一下，你的脸遍布这些墙。
- I would look good on a wall.
我挂在墙上一定很好看。
- And after the election, we can get your mat.
选举结束后，我们可以给你弄个垫子。
What do you say, Nicky?
你怎么说，Nicky？
Are you in?
你加入吗？
- I'm in.
我加入。
- Yes, you'll make a great vice president.
是的，你会成为一个很棒的副总统。
- No, I'm gonna run for president.
不，我要竞选总统。
- What?
- 什么？
- Well, if I have all the power, why do I need you?
- 嗯，如果我拥有所有权力，我为什么还需要你？
I mean, I could get my own mat.
我的意思是，我可以自己买个垫子。
I could get two mats.
我可以买两个垫子。
I could get a guy named Matt and stand on him!
我可以找个叫马特的人，然后站在他身上！
- But--but you can't run for president.
- 但是——但是你不能竞选总统。
- Oh, I'm running, baby.
- 哦，我正在竞选，宝贝。
- Wait, now you're running for president?
- 等等，现在你要竞选总统了？
- Well, it doesn't matter who's president.
- 嗯，谁当总统都无所谓。
You'll all be working for me, the vice president.
你们都得为我工作，我这个副总统。
- Dicky, vice president is below president.
迪基，副总统的职位在总统之下。
- What? Since when?
什么？从什么时候开始的？
That's it. I'm running for president.
就这样，我要竞选总统。
- No!
不行！
- Looks like it's every Quad for himself.
看来是各自为战了。
- Or herself.
或者各自为己。
- Or me-self.
或者我为自己。
- ♪ Oh, oh ♪
哦，哦
- Vote for Dawn, and we'll have a ball!
投给唐恩，我们会玩得开心！
- Remember, a vote for Dicky is a vote for me.
记住，投给迪基就是投给我。
- Hey, campaign somewhere else.
嘿，去别的地方宣传吧。
This is my spot.
这是我的地盘。
- There is no spots.
这里没有地盘之分。
- Oh, there are spots,
哦，有地盘的，
and you're both in mine.
而且你们俩都在我的地盘里。
- Are you kidding me? - What are you talking about? - That is ridiculous. - This whole thing is my spot.
你在开玩笑吗？ - 你在说什么？ - 这太荒谬了。 - 整个地方都是我的地盘。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- What's going on?
发生什么事了？
- Yeah, everyone is laughing at us.
是啊，大家都在笑我们。
- This may be why.
这可能就是原因。
- These three Harpers sleep and sleep and sleep.
这三个哈珀家的人睡了又睡，睡了又睡。
They're so tired,
他们太累了，
they spend up to eight hours a night sleeping.
每晚要睡上八个小时。
You could even say they hibernate.
你甚至可以说他们在冬眠。
You know what else hibernates?
你知道还有什么冬眠吗？
Bears.
熊。
That's right.
没错。
Nicky, Dicky, and Dawn are bears.
尼基、迪基和道恩都是熊。
Do you really want your president to be a bear?
你真的希望你的总统是一只熊吗？
I didn't think so.
我想你不会的。
Vote for Ricky, the only human in the race.
投票给Ricky，比赛中唯一的人类。
Paid for by Ricky Harper's allowance.
由Ricky Harper的零花钱赞助。
- Bears?
- 熊？
- I'm not a bear.
- 我不是熊。
- Yeah, me neither.
- 对，我也不是。
- Hey, what up, bears?
- 嘿，怎么了，熊们？
I'm guessing you saw my new campaign video.
我猜你看到了我的新竞选视频。
Oh, and look.
哦，看。
Now I'm winning.
现在我领先了。
all: Not for long.
大家：不会太久的。
- Ricky was the last of The Quads to be potty trained.
- Ricky是The Quads中最后一个接受如厕训练的。
Do you really want him to be president?
你真的想让他当总统吗？
- [crying]
- [哭泣]
- He's an accident waiting to happen.
- 他是个随时可能发生事故的人。
Vote Nicky Harper for president.
为Nicky Harper投票竞选总统。
- This is Dawn Harper...
- 这是Dawn Harper...
biting the head off an innocent marshmallow bunny.
咬掉一个无辜棉花糖兔子的头。
Imagine what she'd do to a real bunny.
想象她会对一只真兔子做什么。
- Nicky, Ricky, and Dicky seemed focused, but on what?
- Nicky、Ricky和Dicky看似专注，但究竟在专注什么？
- Get them!
- 抓住他们！
- Destroy!
- 摧毁！
- I'm a machine!
- 我是一台机器！
- World destruction,
- 世界毁灭，
because they're robots.
因为他们是机器人。
Stop the evil robots.
阻止邪恶的机器人。
♪ ♪
- Ah!
- 啊！
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- How could you do this to me, Anne?
- 你怎么能这样对我，安妮？
- Do what? I just posted a photo where I look really good.
- 做什么？我只是发了一张我看起来很棒的照片。
- Yeah, while I was next to you in the middle of a big sneeze.
是啊，我当时正站在你旁边打了个大喷嚏。
[knocking]
[敲门声]
People are knocking like crazy, Anne.
安妮，人们疯狂地敲门呢。
- Oh, yikes.
哦，天哪。
You do look terrible.
你看起来确实很糟糕。
Oh, well.
哦，好吧。
- Oh, that is it.
哦，够了。
- What are you doing? - Getting revenge.
- 你在干什么？- 报复你呢。
Make a horrible face.
做个鬼脸。
- No, no, you make a horrible face. - No, you make a horrible face. - No way.
- 不，不，你来做个鬼脸。- 不，你来做个鬼脸。- 没门。
- Hey, kids.
嘿，孩子们。
How's the campaign going?
竞选活动进行得怎么样？
- Good. - Wonderful.
很好。
- Great. - Awesome.
太棒了。
- Good, because sometimes petty differences
很棒。
can bring out the worst in people.
太好了，因为有时候小分歧
all: Not us!
会让人暴露出最糟糕的一面。
- Great, can you guys help me bring dinner to the table?
我们不会！
- Will Dicky keep that whole dish of potatoes for himself?
太好了，你们能帮我一起把晚餐端到桌子上吗？
- He will, because he's selfish
迪基会自己霸占那一整盘土豆吗？
and thinks he's the only person
并且他认为自己是唯一
who should be allowed to eat a potato.
有资格吃土豆的人。
- He says potato, I say p-greedy!
- 他说是土豆，我说是贪婪！
Vote for Dawn!
投给Dawn一票！
- Dad, can you serve me some potatoes?
- 爸爸，能给我盛点土豆吗？
I'm trying to win a campaign.
我正在参加一个竞选。
- Sorry, pal. Bigger fish to fry.
- 抱歉，孩子。有更重要的事要处理。
I'm trying to take a horrible picture of your mother.
我正试图拍一张你妈妈糟糕的照片。
- I'm hungry too.
- 我也饿了。
- Fine.
- 好吧。
- This isn't our best parenting moment.
这不是我们作为父母最光彩的时刻。
- [sighs] No, it's not.
是啊，确实不是。
- You mean the fact that you just
你指的是你刚才
dumped potatoes on the ground
把土豆扔到地上
or the fact that he is eating them?
还是他正在吃它们的事实？
Vote for Dawn.
请投票给Dawn。
♪ ♪
- Okay, final call.
好了，最后呼吁。
Get your votes in.
快来投票吧。
If you vote for me, I will come to your house
如果你投票给我，我会去你家
and teach your whole family how to double Dutch.
我会教你全家如何跳双绳。
- I'll come to your house and make a Dutch chocolate cake.
我会去你家做荷兰巧克力蛋糕。
- I'll teach you to speak Dutch.
我会教你讲荷兰语。
- I'll give you a new nickname, and that nickname will be Dutch.
我会给你一个新的昵称，那个昵称就是荷兰。
- Oh, the scatterplot thickens.
哦，散点图变得更复杂了。
- What, Dicky won?
什么，迪基赢了？
- I won?
我赢了？
Sweet!
太棒了！
I hereby cancel school forever.
我在此宣布学校永远关闭。
[cheering]
[欢呼]
- No, Dicky.
- 不，Dicky。
It was a four-way tie.
这是四人平局。
You'll all have to share being president.
你们都得分享总统的位置。
all: What?
所有人：什么？
[bell rings]
[铃声响起]
- Share?
- 分享？
This is worse than losing to you.
这比输给你还糟糕。
- Does that mean I still have to make
- 那是不是意味着我还得做
all those Dutch chocolate cakes?
所有那些荷兰巧克力蛋糕？
- Well, I voted for you, so yeah, I'm gonna want mine.
- 嗯，我投票给你了，所以是的，我要我的那一份。
- You know what?
你知道吗？
I admit I did some things in this campaign
我承认在这场竞选中我做了一些
that I'm not proud of, but I only got carried away
我不引以为傲的事，但我只是被冲昏了头
because I really wanted to be president,
因为我真的很想当主席，
so I could serve our school.
这样我就能为我们学校服务。
You guys only wanted to win because you wanted to beat me,
你们只是想赢，因为你们想打败我，
so the three of you can share it.
所以你们三个可以共享这个荣誉。
I'm out.
我退出了。
I'm sure you'll do a great job running the class fundraisers
我相信你们会做得很好，管理班级筹款活动
and attending the student council meetings
和参加学生会会议
every day after school and doing the monthly budget.
每天放学后和处理每月的预算。
I'm sure you'll do fine with all the math.
我确信你们在数学方面会做得很好。
So congratulations, Mr. and Mr. and Miss President.
所以，恭喜了，总统先生们和小姐。
- Wow.
哇。
He is mad at you guys.
他生你们的气了。
- ♪ Oh, oh, hey, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
哦，哦，嘿，哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
- Um, Ricky, we thought about what you said,
嗯，Ricky，我们考虑了你说的，
and we feel really bad for ruining your thing.
我们真的为毁了你的事情感到很难过。
- You were right.
你说得对。
We were all doing it for the wrong reasons.
我们都是出于错误的原因在做这件事。
- So we decided to give up the presidency.
所以我们决定放弃总统职位。
- You did?
你们真的这么做了？
- Yeah, and Mr. Williams agreed to make you the only president.
是的，而且威廉姆斯先生同意让你成为唯一的总统。
- Congratulations.
恭喜你。
- Uh-huh, you guys just didn't want
嗯，你们只是不想做所有的工作，对吧？
to do all the work, did you?
是的。
- Yep. - Nailed it.
说中了。
- Math.
数学。
- Well, thank you guys.
好吧，谢谢你们。
I really appreciate it.
我真的很感激。
That was very mature of you.
你表现得非常成熟。
- I feel good about this.
- 我对此感觉很好。
- He's gonna make a great president.
- 他会成为一个伟大的总统。
- And he seems humble.
- 而且他看起来很谦逊。
[horn blows]
[喇叭声]
- Ha!
- 哈！
Fooled you!
骗到你了！
Being class president is easy.
当班级总统很容易。
I made up all those jobs, so you'd drop out.
那些工作都是我编的，这样你才会退出。
I did it!
我做到了！
I'm class president!
我是班长！
Whoo!
喔！
[horn blows]
[号角声]
- Wow, dude, you are good.
哇，伙计，你真行。
- Yeah, I'm not even mad.
是啊，我甚至不生气。
I'm just impressed.
我只是佩服。
- You were right, Ricky.
你说得对，里基。
This really is your thing.
这确实是你的强项。
May I take your picture, Mr. President?
我可以给你拍照吗，总统先生？
- Sure.
当然可以。
- Spider! - Ah!
- 蜘蛛！ - 啊！
How does it look?
看起来怎么样？
- Perfect.
- 完美。
This is going straight on FaceShack.
这直接上传到FaceShack。
- Let me see that.
- 让我看看。
- Nope!
- 不行！
[horn blows] - Come here! - Whoo-hoo-hoo!
[喇叭声] - 过来！ - 哇哈哈！
- Dawn!
- 黎明！
[horn blowing]
[喇叭声]
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 纳纳纳纳纳纳纳纳纳纳纳纳纳纳 ♪
[whistling]
♪ [口哨声] ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶耶耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶耶耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪